Don't panic at all and write the paper well.  Yes
?  Go quickly.
hello.  My name is Raghav and this is my village
Anantapur.  I live here with my entire family
and everyone here earns their livelihood with great hard work and
dedication.  Let me introduce
you to some of my friends.  This
is the sun.  Teaches children in school.
How are you?  And this is Mansoor Miyan.
He has a ration shop.  How are you Mansoor Mian?
Everything alright?  This is Madan ji.  He has a tractor repair
shop.
We all have the same dream.  Stayed in a pucca house for a day.
Have a good life.  Give good education to our children.   Get
them married with great pomp and show.  And then
spend your old age happily and peacefully.  That is why everyone
saves the money they earn.  Some of it goes
into business,
some into fulfilling daily needs
and sometimes into helping each other.  But
what about dreams?  How will we fulfill them
?
One day all four friends were talking about this at the Chaupal,
Namaste.  I am Rakesh and this is my
colleague Sheela ji.  We were passing through here.   When I
heard you, I came here.  If
you have some time, we
will tell you some things so that you can fulfill your dreams.  Yes,
please sit.
Look, we have some plans
that will protect you and your family
so that you can fulfill your dreams.   First of all,
we would like to tell you about our company.
We both are
Life Insurance Advisors at Birla Sun Life Insurance.  That
means we advise people to get insurance.
We
will help you and your family by getting the right insurance plan.
Birla Sun Life Insurance is one of the
leading private sector life insurance
companies in India.  Birla Sun Life
Insurance is a part of the Aditya Birla Group
which is one of the largest industrial houses in India.
Aditya Birla Group is at the
forefront in whatever field it does business.  Aditya Birla
Group has branches spread across 25 countries and six continents.
That's all fine Rakesh
ji, but if you have any doubt in your mind then tell me.
There is no doubt that your company
is very big.  But
how will your company help us to fulfill our dreams?  Your question
is absolutely correct.  A lot of Aditya Birla Group's
business is spread across rural areas.
Therefore, we know very well the needs and aspirations of our rural brothers.
We also believe that Bhima
is an area which
helps in the development of our village and the people living in the village
and we all know that the lifeline of India
resides in its villages.
To fulfill your dreams, our company has now
brought a guaranteed savings plan
which has been designed keeping your specific needs in mind.
In this plan, you
save a little money every year which
continues till the end of the plan.
You get guaranteed love after completion of the plan period.
Guaranteed love.  Yes, guaranteed love.  First of all
you get guaranteed maturity
love.  This means that after completion of the plan period,
you get guaranteed return of money and
also have the possibility of earning more money.  This
means that you not only get guaranteed savings but
also get the opportunity to earn more
because your money is
invested in government securities.
If
you need the money during the plan period, you
can also get it back.  If you wish, you can
also surrender the plan after completion of 3 years of the plan.
This plan protects
your family from financial loss in case of any accidental incident
and the best part is
that its security cover increases every year.
This plan also gives you the opportunity to avail Survival Benefit at the end of every policy year
after 3 years.
You can either withdraw it in cash or
use it to pay the remaining insurance premium.
If you wish, you can withdraw the money in small amounts to meet your needs
or to pay the next premium of this plan.
And the
most special thing about this plan is that if you want, you can
also take a loan from Birla Sunlife Insurance against this insurance plan.  Wow,
so many benefits in one plan,
Rakesh ji, how much paperwork will be required and
how much running around will I have to do?  You don't have to
worry about that at all.  Keeping your every convenience in
mind, we have opened
Birla Sun Life Insurance branches and
insurance centers nearby.  You just have to
go to those centres.  Our
people will take care of everything else and answer all your questions.
Rakesh ji, Sheela ji, I wish there was a
guarantee of good rains this year.
Birla Sunlife Insurance offers
Guaranteed Savings
Plans that give you guaranteed benefits in every situation, giving
you complete peace of mind.
[Music]